<resources>
    <string name="app_name">One Punch Man Trainer</string>
    <string name="shared_file_key">shared file key</string>
    <string name="first_time">first time?</string>
    <string name="male_or_fem">male or fem?</string>
    <string name="haircolor_chosen">Chosen haircolor</string>
    <string name="hair_percent">Latest hairpercent</string>
    <string name="last_day">Last day</string>
    <string name="last_month">Last month</string>
    <string name="last_year">Last year</string>
    <string name="completed_running">Completed running</string>
    <string name="completed_pushups">Completed pushups</string>
    <string name="completed_squats">Completed squats</string>
    <string name="completed_situps">Completed situps</string>
    <string name="first_time_training">First time in training activity</string>
    <string name="help_dialog_text">Click on your avatar in order to change haircolor or gender.
        \n\nClick on one of the exercise-buttons to start exercising.
        \n\nThe completed exercises will have green buttons.
        \n\nYour result will be measured in hairloss.
        \n\nThe only way to become stronger is to train until your hair falls off..</string>
    <string name="ok">Got it!</string>
    <string name="permission_accelerometer">This app needs the accelerometer in your phone to
        measure steps, squats and sit-ups. Without it there is no way to measure your result or
        see your progress.
        \n\nIf you can no longer allow access through the app you can change it if you go to:
        Settings > Applications > One Punch Man Trainer > Permissions</string>
    <string name="ok_2">Okay</string>
    <string name="start_help">In this app you will go through the same training as One Punch Man.
        \nIf you are new to training be careful not to over exert or strain yourself.
    \nMake sure to eat at least three meals per day (a banana for breakfast is fine).
    \n\nGood luck!</string>
    <string name="character_help">Before you start training you need to create an avatar.
    You can always change your avatar later.</string>
    <string name="running_guide">The step counter is set to only record big movements. Therefore it
        might not give an accurate result if you are just walking. Make sure to run in order
    for the sensor to work properly.\n\nGood luck!</string>
    <string name="pushup_guide">Keep your back as straight as possible and touch your nose on the
    screen on the way down.\n\nGood luck!</string>
    <string name="squat_guide">Make sure to have proper form (look at the example) and do the squats
    nice and slow. That way you will get the most out of your training as well as a more accurate
    reading.\n\nGood luck!</string>
    <string name="situp_guide">Make sure to have proper form (look at the example) and do the
        sit-upsnice and slow. That way you will get the most out of your training as well as a more
        accurate reading.\n\nGood luck!</string>
    <string name="exercise_type">The specific exercise.</string>
    <string name="same_date">Is this the same date?</string>
    <string name="running_count">This is the running count</string>
    <string name="pushup_count">This is the pushup count</string>
    <string name="squat_count">This is the squat count</string>
    <string name="situp_count">This is the situp count</string>
    <string name="from_training">The intent came from the training activity</string>
</resources>